Guide to the Language Resource Center collection, circa 1963-1983.
Language Resource Center collection,
- Reel-to-reel tape recordings
  - Unknown
    - Waray Peace Corps Tapes, 1968; TR-14445; Wolff, J. U. (Box 16)
      LRC #: WA 11
    - Waray Peace Corps Tapes, 1968; TR-14446; Wolff, J. U. (Box 16)
      LRC #: WA 12
    - Waray tape fix, Undated; TR-14447 (Box 16)
      LRC #: WA
    - Stories from Waray, Undated; TR-14448 (Box 16)
    - Waray - Northern Waray, Undated; TR-14449 (Box 16)
    - Interview with Children, Christmas, Undated; TR-14450 (Box 16)
      LRC #: WA ?
    - Waray tape, Undated; TR-14451 (Box 16)
      LRC #: WA 2b
    - Stories from Tacloban, Undated; TR-14452 (Box 16)
    - El Tzeltal Hablado, Undated; TR-14453; McQuown; Castro (Box 17)
      LRC #: TZ 1
    - El Tzeltal Hablado, Undated; TR-14454; McQuown; Castro (Box 17)
      LRC #: TZ 2
    - El Tzeltal Hablado, Undated; TR-14455; McQuown; Castro (Box 17)
      LRC #: TZ 3
    - El Tzeltal Hablado, Undated; TR-14456; McQuown; Castro (Box 17)
      LRC #: TZ 4
    - El Tzeltal Hablado, Undated; TR-14457; McQuown; Castro (Box 17)
      LRC #: TZ 5
    - El Tzeltal Hablado, Undated; TR-14458; McQuown; Castro (Box 17)
      LRC #: TZ 6
    - El Tzeltal Hablado, Undated; TR-14459; McQuown; Castro (Box 17)
      LRC #: TZ 7
    - El Tzeltal Hablado, Undated; TR-14460; McQuown; Castro (Box 17)
      LRC #: TZ 8
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14461; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 1
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14462; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 2
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14463; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 3
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14464; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 4
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14465; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 5
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14466; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 6
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14467; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 7
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14468; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 8
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14469; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 9
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14470; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 10
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14471; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 11
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14472; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 12
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14473; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 13
    - Spoken (Yucatec) Maya, Undated; TR-14474; Blair, R.; Vermont, R. (Box 17)
      LRC #: YM 14
    - Undated, TR-14475; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 1-1
    - Undated, TR-14476; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 1-2
    - Undated, TR-14477; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 1-3
    - Undated, TR-14478; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 1-4
    - Undated, TR-14479; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 2
    - Undated, TR-14480; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 3
    - Undated, TR-14481; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 4
    - Undated, TR-14482; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 5
    - Undated, TR-14483; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 6
    - Undated, TR-14484; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 7
    - Undated, TR-14485; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 8
    - Undated, TR-14486; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 9
    - Undated, TR-14487; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 10
    - Undated, TR-14488; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 11
    - Undated, TR-14489; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 12
    - Undated, TR-14490; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 13
    - Undated, TR-14491; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 14
    - Undated, TR-14492; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 15
    - Undated, TR-14493; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 16
    - Undated, TR-14494; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 17
    - Undated, TR-14495; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 18
    - Undated, TR-14496; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 19
    - Undated, TR-14497; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: TWI 20
    - Vergil: Aeneid (from I and II), 1977; TR-14498 (Box 39)
      Read by R. Williams
      LRC #: LAT 1
    - The Sounds of Language — Afrikaans, Undated; TR-14499; University of California, Berkeley (Box 39)
      LRC #: LQ 2
    - Kru (Liberia), 1975; TR-14500; Mariah, Augustus B.; Grimes, J. E.; University of Oklahoma (Box 39)
      LRC #: KR
    - New Guinea Pidgin, 1975; TR-14501; Grimes, J.E. (Box 39)
      LRC #: PNG
    - Tapes in Kamayu, Undated; TR-14502 (Box 39)
      LRC #: KAM 1, 3
    - Tapes in Kamayu, 1971; TR-14503 (Box 39)
      LRC #: KAM 2
    - Japanese for Business Purposes, 1980; TR-14504; Jorden, Eleanor (Box 45)
      LRC #: JPB 6.1
    - Japanese for Business Purposes, 1980; TR-14505; Jorden, Eleanor (Box 45)
      LRC #: JPB 6.2
    - Japanese for Business Purposes, 1980; TR-14506; Jorden, Eleanor (Box 45)
      LRC #: JPB 7.1
    - Japanese for Business Purposes, 1980; TR-14507; Jorden, Eleanor (Box 45)
      LRC #: JPB 8.1
    - Japanese for Business Purposes, 1980; TR-14508; Jorden, Eleanor (Box 45)
      LRC #: JPB 9.1
    - Anthology of Yugoslavian Literature, 1977; TR-14509; Jugoton records (Box 45)
      LRC #: YA 1
    - Anthology of Yugoslavian Literature, 1977; TR-14510; Jugoton records (Box 45)
      LRC #: YA 2
    - Anthology of Yugoslavian Literature, 1977; TR-14511; Jugoton records (Box 45)
      LRC #: YA 3
    - Anthology of Yugoslavian Literature, 1977; TR-14512; Jugoton records (Box 45)
      LRC #: YA 4
    - Anthology of Yugoslavian Literature, 1977; TR-14513; Jugoton records (Box 45)
      LRC #: YA 5
    - Anthology of Yugoslavian Literature, 1977; TR-14514; Jugoton records (Box 45)
      LRC #: YA 6
    - Intro to Modern Lithuanian, 1979; TR-14515; Schmalstieg (Box 45)
      LRC #: LI 1.1
    - Intro to Modern Lithuanian, 1979; TR-14516; Schmalstieg (Box 45)
      LRC #: LI 1.2
    - Intro to Modern Lithuanian, 1979; TR-14517; Schmalstieg (Box 45)
      LRC #: LI 1.3
    - Intro to Modern Lithuanian, 1979; TR-14518; Schmalstieg (Box 45)
      LRC #: LI 1.4
    - Intro to Modern Lithuanian, 1979; TR-14519; Schmalstieg (Box 45)
      LRC #: LI 2.1
    - Intro to Modern Lithuanian, 1979; TR-14520; Schmalstieg (Box 45)
      LRC #: LI 2.2
    - Intro to Modern Lithuanian, 1979; TR-14521; Schmalstieg (Box 45)
      LRC #: LI 2.3
    - Intro to Modern Lithuanian, 1979; TR-14522; Schmalstieg (Box 45)
      LRC #: LI 2.4
    - Lithuanian intonation and pronunciation, 1967; TR-14523; Lithuanian Institute of Education (Box 45)
      LRC #: LI 3
    - Undated, TR-14524 (Box 45)
      LRC #: EPM 1
    - Undated, TR-14525 (Box 45)
      LRC #: EPM 2
    - English, Undated; TR-14526; Feldman, Richard (Box 45)
      LRC #: ERF 3
    - 3 Poems by Robert Frost, Undated; TR-14527 (Box 45)
      LRC #: ERF 6
    - Welcome to English, Undated; TR-14528; Sheeler, Willard D.; Feldman, Richard (Box 45)
      LRC #: EWE 1
    - Welcome to English, Undated; TR-14529; Sheeler, Willard D.; Feldman, Richard (Box 45)
      LRC #: EWE 2
    - Corny English Songs by Ozzie and Harriet, Undated; TR-14530 (Box 47)
      LRC #: LVR 8
    - Oral Interviews, Undated; TR-14531; Jones, Randy (Box 47)
      LRC #: LPT 1
    - Oral Interviews, Undated; TR-14532; Jones, Randy (Box 47)
      LRC #: LPT 2
    - DML Demonstrations in German, French, Spanish, Undated; TR-14533 (Box 47)
      LRC #: ZLM 2
    - Examples from Structure of Intonational Meaning, TR-14534; Ladd, D. R. (Box 47)
      LRC #: LRL 1
    - Russian Poetry for Intermediates, Undated; TR-14535 (Box 47)
      LRC #: RRL 25
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1977-08-08-; TR-14536; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 1
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1977-08-09-; TR-14537; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 2
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1977-08-10-; TR-14538; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 3
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1977-08-11-; TR-14539; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 4
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1975; TR-14540; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 5
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1975; TR-14541; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 6
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1975; TR-14542; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 7
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1975; TR-14543; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 8
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1975; TR-14544; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 9
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1975; TR-14545; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 10
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1980; TR-14546; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 28
    - Graded Russian Reader, 1980; TR-14547; Zoschencko, M. (Box 47)
      LRC #: RQ 29
    - What I Saw: Beginning Russian Reader, Undated; TR-14548 (Box 47)
      LRC #: RWH 2
    - What I Saw: Beginning Russian Reader, Undated; TR-14549 (Box 47)
      LRC #: RWH 3
    - What I Saw: Beginning Russian Reader, Undated; TR-14550 (Box 47)
      LRC #: RWH 4
    - What I Saw: Beginning Russian Reader, Undated; TR-14551 (Box 47)
      LRC #: RWH 5
    - Yoruba, 1988; TR-14552; Laniran, Yetunde (Box 47)
      LRC #: YRL 1
    - Yoruba, 1988; TR-14553; Laniran, Yetunde (Box 47)
      LRC #: YRL 2
    - Yoruba, 1988; TR-14554; Laniran, Yetunde (Box 47)
      LRC #: YRL 3
    - Yoruba, 1988; TR-14555; Laniran, Yetunde (Box 47)
      LRC #: YRL 4
    - Yoruba, 1988; TR-14556; Laniran, Yetunde (Box 47)
      LRC #: YRL 5
    - Yoruba, 1988; TR-14557; Laniran, Yetunde (Box 47)
      LRC #: YRL 6
    - Fortschritt Deutsch, Undated; TR-14558 (Box 47)
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14559; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 1
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14560; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 2
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14561; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 3
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14562; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 4
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14563; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 5
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14564; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 6
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14565; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 7
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14566; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 8
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14567; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 9
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14568; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 10
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14569; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 11
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14570; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 12
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14571; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 13
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14572; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 14
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14573; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 15
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14574; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 16
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14575; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 17
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14576; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 18
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14577; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 19
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14578; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 20
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14579; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 21
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14580; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 22
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14581; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 23
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14582; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 24
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14583; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 25
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14584; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 26
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14585; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 27
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14586; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 28
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14587; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 29
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14588; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 30
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14589; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 31
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14590; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 32
    - Nine Lectures on Russian Poetry, 1976; TR-14591; Jacobson, Roman; Harvard (Box 49)
      LRC #: RA 33
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14592 (Box 49)
      These tapes are a collection of interviews of Hawaiian natives of various backgrounds.
      LRC #: LMI 1
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14593 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 2
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14594 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 3
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14595 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 4
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14596 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 5
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14597 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 6
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14598 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 7
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14599 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 8
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14600 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 9
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14601 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 10
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14602 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 11
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14603 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 12
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14604 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 13
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14605 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 14
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14606 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 15
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14607 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 16
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14608 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 17
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14609 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 18
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14610 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 19
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14611 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 20
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14612 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 21
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14613 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 22
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14614 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 23
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, Undated; TR-14615 (Box 49)
      LRC #: LMI 24
    - We Learn Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14616; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 3
    - We Learn Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14617; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 4
    - We Learn Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14618; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 5
    - We Learn Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14619; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 6
    - We Learn Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14620; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 7
    - We Learn Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14621; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 8
    - We Learn Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14622; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 9
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14623; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 10
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14624; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 11
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14625; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 12
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14626; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 13
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14627; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 14
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14628; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 15
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14629; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 16
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14630; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 17
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14631; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 18
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14632; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 19
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14633; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 20
    - We Speak Serbo-Croatian, Undated; TR-14634; Barac-Kostrencic, et. al. (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCU 21
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14635 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 1
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14636 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 2
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14637 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 3
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14638 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 4
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14639 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 5
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14640 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 6
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14641 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 7
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14642 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 8
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14643 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 9
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14644 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 10
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14645 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 11
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14646 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 12
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14647 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 13
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14648 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 14
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14649 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 15
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14650 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 16
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14651 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 17
    - Serbo-Croatian AudioVisual Course, 1975; TR-14652 (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCA 18
    - Andric (readings from and about), 1976-05-06; TR-14653; Milanovic, Branko (Box 62)
      LRC #: SCR 1
    - What I Saw: Beginning Russian Reader, Undated; TR-14654 (Box 63)
      LRC #: RWH 1
    - Intermediate Russian Dialogues, Undated; TR-14655 (Box 63)
      LRC #: RID 1
    - Intermediate Russian Dialogues, Undated; TR-14656 (Box 63)
      LRC #: RID 2
    - Intermediate Russian Dialogues, Undated; TR-14657 (Box 63)
      LRC #: RID 3
    - Russian Dialects, Undated; TR-14658 (Box 63)
      LRC #: RDI 1
    - Russian Dialects, Undated; TR-14659 (Box 63)
      LRC #: RDI 2
    - Russian Dialects, Undated; TR-14660 (Box 63)
      LRC #: RDI 3
    - Intermediate Russian, Undated; TR-14661 (Box 63)
      LRC #: RIT 1
    - Intermediate Russian, Undated; TR-14662 (Box 63)
      LRC #: RIT 2
    - Intermediate Russian, Undated; TR-14663 (Box 63)
      LRC #: RIT 3
    - Intermediate Russian, Undated; TR-14664 (Box 63)
      LRC #: RIT 4
    - Advanced Russian - 2nd Edition (spliced master), Undated; TR-14665 (Box 63)
    - Advanced Russian - 2nd Edition (spliced master), Undated; TR-14666 (Box 63)
    - Advanced Russian - 2nd Edition (spliced master), Undated; TR-14667 (Box 63)
    - Advanced Russian - 2nd Edition (spliced master), Undated; TR-14668 (Box 63)
    - Advanced Russian, Undated; TR-14669 (Box 63)
    - Advanced Russian - 2nd Edition (spliced master), Undated; TR-14670 (Box 63)
    - Georgian, Undated; TR-14671; Brown, Wayles (Box 63)
      LRC #: GEO 1
    - Various Linguistic Recordings, Undated; TR-14672 (Box 63)
      J.M. Cowan’s retirement party
      LRC #: LVR 7
    - Spoken Tamil, Undated; TR-14673 (Box 64)
      LRC #: TA 1
    - Spoken Tamil, Undated; TR-14674 (Box 64)
      LRC #: TA 2
    - Spoken Tamil, Undated; TR-14675 (Box 64)
      LRC #: TA 3
    - Spoken Tamil, Undated; TR-14676 (Box 64)
      LRC #: TA 4
    - Spoken Tamil, Undated; TR-14677 (Box 64)
      LRC #: TA 5
    - Spoken Tamil, Undated; TR-14678 (Box 64)
      LRC #: TA 6
    - Spoken Tamil, Undated; TR-14679 (Box 64)
      LRC #: TA 7
    - Spoken Tamil, Undated; TR-14680 (Box 64)
      LRC #: TA 8
    - Spoken Tamil, Undated; TR-14681 (Box 64)
      LRC #: TA 9
    - Spoken Tamil, Undated; TR-14682 (Box 64)
      LRC #: TA 10
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14683; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 1
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14684; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 2
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14685; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 3
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14686; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 4
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14687; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 4B
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14688; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 5A
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14689; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 5B
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14690; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 6A
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14691; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 6B
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14692; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 7
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14693; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 8
    - A Basic Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14694; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUB 9
    - Intermediate Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14695; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUI 1
    - Intermediate Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14696; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUI 2
    - Intermediate Course in Susu, Undated; TR-14697; Waugh; Faber (Box 65)
      LRC #: SUI 3
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14698; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 3
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14699; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 4
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14700; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 5
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14701; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 6
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14702; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 7
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14703; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 8
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14704; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 9
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14705; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 10
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14706; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 11
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14707; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 12
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14708; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 13
    - A Basic Course in Modern Telugh, Undated; TR-14709; Krishnamurti (Box 65)
      LRC #: TE 14
    - Igbo, Undated; TR-14710 (Box 65)
      LRC #: IG 1
    - Igbo, Undated; TR-14711 (Box 65)
      LRC #: IG 2
    - Igbo, Undated; TR-14712 (Box 65)
      LRC #: IG 3
    - Igbo, Undated; TR-14713 (Box 65)
      LRC #: IG 4
    - Igbo, Undated; TR-14714 (Box 65)
      LRC #: IG 5
    - Igbo, Undated; TR-14715 (Box 65)
      LRC #: IG 6
    - Igbo, Undated; TR-14716 (Box 65)
      LRC #: IG 7
    - Igbo, Undated; TR-14717 (Box 65)
      LRC #: IG 8
    - Igbo, Undated; TR-14718 (Box 65)
      LRC #: IG 9